export const questions = [
    [ {    
        numb:1,
        question:"What is the main Ingredient of an happy man?",
        answer:"Contentment",
        option:[
            "Hardwork",
            "Contentment",
            "Greed",
            "Money"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:2,
        question:"Nigeria would have been a total hell if not for _____",
        answer:"Cruise",
        option:[
            "Cruise",
            "Money",
            "Food",
            "Music"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:3,
        question:" Haa! 'Adulthood na scam' ",
        answer:"You better get am for your mind",
        option:[
            "If you know,you know",
            "I'm telling you dear",
            "You better get am for your mind",
            "You'll get to know soon"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:4,
        question:" 'Maa dira oooo' ",
        answer:"Iku a pa e",
        option:[
            "Gone to soon",
            "Wa a ku danu",
            "You go soon collect",
            "Iku a pa e"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:5,
        question:"Is relationship really scam?",
        answer:"Yes,Na mumu dey love",
        option:[
            "Yes,breakfast ends all",
            "Yes,Na mumu dey love",
            "Maybe or Maybe not",
            "Yes,love hurts"

        ]
    },
    {    
       numb:6,
       question:" Bonjour is a/an _____ word ",
       answer:"French",
       option:[
           "German",
           "French",
           "Yoruba",
           "Igbo"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:7,
       question:"Bring FrontEnd works",
       answer:"It is my turn",
       option:[
           "Trial will convince you",
           "I deserve  it",
           "It is my turn",
           "I can handle it"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:8,
       question:"Okay, you wanna get everything,right? lol..Examiner's mark",
       answer:"No correct option",
       option:[
           "It's unfair oo",
           "TOOBAD maa pami nah",
           "Fantabulous",
           "Wonderful"

       ]
   }],
   
   
   

   //  second question
    [ {    
        numb:1,
        question:"The very first time-consuming '2go' star progress is ___",
        answer:"Professional",
        option:[
            "Master",
            "Professional",
            "Expert",
            "Novice"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:2,
        question:"How many month(s) has 28 days?",
        answer:"Twelve",
        option:[
            "February",
            "One",
            "June",
            "Twelve"

        ]
    },
    {    
        numb:3,
        question:"Haa! 'Relationship na scam' ",
        answer:"U better get am for your mind",
        option:[
            "I'm telling you dear",
            "U better get am for your mind",
            "If you know,you know",
            "Swears"

        ]
    },
    
   {    
       numb:4,
       question:"Bring FrontEnd works",
       answer:"It is my turn",
       option:[
           "Trial will convince you",
           "I deserve  it",
           "It is my turn",
           "I can handle it"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:5,
       question:" 'Komao' is a/an _____ word  ",
       answer:"Korean",
       option:[
           "Nigerian",
           "American",
           "Korean",
           "Hausa"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:6,
       question:"Nigeria would have been a total hell if not for ______",
       answer:"Cruise",
       option:[
           "Cruise",
           "Money",
           "Food",
           "Music"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:7,
       question:"Who is the founder of 'Maa dira ooo'?",
       answer:"Oba Solomon",
       option:[
           "Oba Solomon",
           "Alabi Williams",
           "Olalere Babatunde",
           "B.O.D"

       ]
   },
   {    
       numb:8,
       question:"Okay, you wanna get everything,right? lol..Examiner's mark",
       answer:"No correct option",
       option:[
           "It's unfair oo",
           "TOOBAD maa pami nah",
           "Fantabulous",
           "Wonderful"

       ]
   },
   
   

],

// third question
[{    
   numb:1,
   question:"The most means of living among youth is ____ ",
   answer:"Jama-Jama",
   option:[
       "Crypto",
       "Software Development",
       "Jama-Jama",
       "Entertainment"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:2,
   question:"October 20, 2020 ",
   answer:"Forever in our heart",
   option:[
       "Forever in our heart",
       "What happen to it?",
       "Sighs",
       "It's  well"

   ]
},

{    
   numb:3,
   question:"Majority can still cope without _____?",
   answer:"Personal ride",
   option:[
       "Food",
       "Data",
       "Personal ride",
       "Music"

   ]
},

{    
   numb:4,
   question:"Who is the founder of 'Emi lokan' ?",
   answer:"Baba Agbalagba",
   option:[
       "Baba Agbalagba",
       "TOOBAD",
       "Baddest",
       "I no sabi"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:5,
   question:" Girl,I know you look so fine ......",
   answer:"And I want you to be mine",
   option:[
       "I'm for real",
       "Omo toh shan",
       "And I want you to be mine",
       "I will take care of you"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:6,
   question:"Nigeria would have been a total hell if not for _____",
   answer:"Cruise",
   option:[
       "Cruise",
       "Money",
       "Food",
       "Music"

   ]
},

{    
   numb:7,
   question:" ____ is not a 2go star-progress  ",
   answer:"Verified",
   option:[
       "Novice",
       "Verified",
       "Expert",
       "Senior"

   ]
},

{    
   numb:8,
   question:"Okay, you wanna get everything,right? lol..Examiner's mark",
   answer:"No correct option",
   option:[
       "It's unfair oo",
       "TOOBAD maa pami nah",
       "Fantabulous",
       "Wonderful"

   ]
},
//    fourth question
],
[
{    
   numb:1,
   question:"If B.A.T should become president, _____",
   answer:"he will surely amaize us",
   option:[
       "Nigeria will change for good",
       "he will surely amaize us",
       "okay ooo",
       "we will be very sorry"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:2,
   question:"Is relationship really scam?",
   answer:"Yes,Na mumu dey love",
   option:[
       "Yes,breakfast ends all",
       "Yes,Na mumu dey love",
       "Maybe or Maybe not",
       "Yes,love hurts"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:3,
   question:"_____ has 28 days",
   answer:"All of the above",
   option:[
       "February",
       "March",
       "September",
       "All of the above"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:4,
   question:"Nigeria would have been a total hell if not for",
   answer:"Cruise",
   option:[
       "Cruise",
       "Money",
       "Food",
       "Music"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:5,
   question:" ____ is a 2go star-progress  ",
   answer:"Novice",
   option:[
       "Novice",
       "Verified",
       "Business",
       "Boss"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:6,
   question:"The most means of living among youth is ____ ",
   answer:"Jama-Jama",
   option:[
       "Crypto",
       "Software Development",
       "Jama-Jama",
       "Entertainment"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:7,
   question:"Majority can still cope without _____?",
   answer:"Personal ride",
   option:[
       "Food",
       "Data",
       "Personal ride",
       "Music"

   ]
},
{    
   numb:8,
   question:"Okay, you wanna get everything,right? lol..Examiner's mark",
   answer:"No correct option",
   option:[
       "It's unfair oo",
       "TOOBAD maa pami nah",
       "Fantabulous",
       "Wonderful"

   ]
},

]
]